<wpt lat="39.996267" lon="-75.748567" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns="http://www.topografix.com/GPX/1/0">
    <time>2008-07-26T07:00:00Z</time>
    <name>GC1EHC5</name>
    <desc>Moms are the Best, TB Exchange by deb3day, Traditional Cache (2/1.5)</desc>
    <url>http://www.geocaching.com/seek/cache_details.aspx?guid=6fdcd8c1-1cac-4714-b929-ea75e3a5e6c9</url>
    <urlname>Moms are the Best, TB Exchange</urlname>
    <sym>Geocache Found</sym>
    <type>Geocache|Traditional Cache</type>
    <groundspeak:cache id="946189" available="False" archived="True" xmlns:groundspeak="http://www.groundspeak.com/cache/1/0">
      <groundspeak:name>Moms are the Best, TB Exchange</groundspeak:name>
      <groundspeak:placed_by>deb3day</groundspeak:placed_by>
      <groundspeak:owner id="1606719">deb3day</groundspeak:owner>
      <groundspeak:type>Traditional Cache</groundspeak:type>
      <groundspeak:container>Regular</groundspeak:container>
      <groundspeak:difficulty>2</groundspeak:difficulty>
      <groundspeak:terrain>1.5</groundspeak:terrain>
      <groundspeak:country>United States</groundspeak:country>
      <groundspeak:state>Pennsylvania</groundspeak:state>
      <groundspeak:short_description html="True">4qt Lock N Lock hidden on the property of one of my favorite
businesses in Thorndale.</groundspeak:short_description>
      <groundspeak:long_description html="True">&lt;font color="#FF0099"&gt;&lt;b&gt;IF YOU DO NOT INTEND ON LOGGING OR MOVING
THE TRACKABLES, PLEASE DO NOT TAKE THEM!!!!! Please remember that
trackables are other people's possessions. If you keep them, you
are STEALING them!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/font&gt; If you are new to caching, please
read up on how to properly log trackables. Please visit
http://www.geocaching.com/track/howto.aspx. As an owner of
trackables, it is extremely frustrating to see them handled
improperly. Proper logging is essential to know where your
trackable is. If you have questions, I will gladly answer them.
Email me!&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
There are no TB Hotels close by, so I thought it was time to create
one. I have been thinking about placing a cache outside of a
business. Since this business is a personal favorite of mine and
the owner knows me from visiting so often, I decided this was the
place. I not only like what is sold here, but I love checking out
the beautiful gardens both outside and inside. Please take some
time to admire all of the beautiful plants. And check out
what&amp;rsquo;s inside, because it is truly the best!&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
This cache has been hidden with the permission of the business
owner. Please respect his property and do NOT disturb any of the
beautiful gardens. The cache is NOT hidden anywhere near his lovely
plants.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
GPS units show the closest road as a small road off of Business Rte
30. This is now a private road, so do not use it. Access should be
from Business Rte 30. Because this is near a business, I would not
recommend doing this after dark. Police may be suspicious of
someone parking near a business at night poking around with a
flashlight.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
The original contents of this are several TB&amp;rsquo;s and Geocoins
that I collected specifically to get this cache started. Dropping
off TB&amp;rsquo;s that need to move on is encouraged. I will try to
keep this stocked with TB's and Geocoins so check back and use the
cache to help some of your travelers along.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
I thank the business owner for allowing me to place my first cache
and for letting all of the geocachers enjoy his gardens.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Please, no swag. I prefer that the TB's be easy to see, and leave
room for more.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Please be careful with the camo and replace it as found.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Congratulations to bpp_picnic for FTF!</groundspeak:long_description>
      <groundspeak:encoded_hints>
      </groundspeak:encoded_hints>
      <groundspeak:logs>
        <groundspeak:log id="136682503">
          <groundspeak:date>2010-11-21T21:50:44Z</groundspeak:date>
          <groundspeak:type>Found it</groundspeak:type>
          <groundspeak:finder id="1790402">dmcassel</groundspeak:finder>
          <groundspeak:text encoded="False">Quick find with dawnie22. </groundspeak:text>
        </groundspeak:log>
        <groundspeak:log id="137830706">
          <groundspeak:date>2010-12-03T20:00:00Z</groundspeak:date>
          <groundspeak:type>Write note</groundspeak:type>
          <groundspeak:finder id="1790402">dmcassel</groundspeak:finder>
          <groundspeak:text encoded="False">Dropped off a geocoin</groundspeak:text>
        </groundspeak:log>
        <groundspeak:log id="199967705">
          <groundspeak:date>2011-11-20T20:00:00Z</groundspeak:date>
          <groundspeak:type>Write note</groundspeak:type>
          <groundspeak:finder id="1790402">dmcassel</groundspeak:finder>
          <groundspeak:text encoded="False">Dropping off a travel bug. </groundspeak:text>
        </groundspeak:log>
      </groundspeak:logs>
      <groundspeak:travelbugs/>
    </groundspeak:cache>
  </wpt>