<wpt lat="40.0066" lon="-75.620583" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns="http://www.topografix.com/GPX/1/0">
    <time>2008-09-27T07:00:00Z</time>
    <name>GC1GNK6</name>
    <desc>Bobby's Toy Box by BKormann, Traditional Cache (1.5/1.5)</desc>
    <url>http://www.geocaching.com/seek/cache_details.aspx?guid=bfef186c-1441-4e24-8f79-d40d8e93ef56</url>
    <urlname>Bobby's Toy Box</urlname>
    <sym>Geocache Found</sym>
    <type>Geocache|Traditional Cache</type>
    <groundspeak:cache id="1009833" available="False" archived="True" xmlns:groundspeak="http://www.groundspeak.com/cache/1/0">
      <groundspeak:name>Bobby's Toy Box</groundspeak:name>
      <groundspeak:placed_by>BKormann</groundspeak:placed_by>
      <groundspeak:owner id="739562">ajkormann</groundspeak:owner>
      <groundspeak:type>Traditional Cache</groundspeak:type>
      <groundspeak:container>Small</groundspeak:container>
      <groundspeak:difficulty>1.5</groundspeak:difficulty>
      <groundspeak:terrain>1.5</groundspeak:terrain>
      <groundspeak:country>United States</groundspeak:country>
      <groundspeak:state>Pennsylvania</groundspeak:state>
      <groundspeak:short_description html="False">Lock-and-lock with toys for kids.</groundspeak:short_description>
      <groundspeak:long_description html="False">Placed with permission from West Whiteland Township.
You are looking for a 4 liter, camo'd lock-and-lock, just to the west of the playground at Boot Road Park in West Whiteland, PA. Please use Parking Entrance coords, do not approach from neighborhood from South.

A kid's cache, stocked with Toys selected by my son, Bobby. Feel free to trade or take a toy. Bobby will be watching this cache, as he has a special interest in it - it has toys! Please try to bring a kid with you since this newest park of West Whiteland is wonderful.

Congrats to deb3day on the FTF.

And don't forget: Play-Cache-Play!

West Whiteland Park Rules:
1. Hours - The parks shall be open between the hours of sunrise and sunset. At sunset, all activities in the parks
shall cease and all persons in the parks shall leave as soon as possible (except for those activities specially
permitted by the Township).
2. Facilities - The reserved use of Township parks such as recreation fields and other facilities by organized
groups or individuals shall be scheduled at the discretion of the Township, a permit shall be issued specifying
the date, time and location of the use and such use shall be subject to any conditions that may be imposed
thereunder.
3. Alcoholic Beverages - No individual or group shall possess or consume any alcoholic and/or intoxicating
beverages in any park unless specifically granted permission by the Board of Supervisors.
4. Personal Conduct – No individual or group shall engage in improper conduct within the parks so as to annoy or
risk injury to any other person using the parks or occupying adjacent property.
5. Disposal of Waste - All waste and garbage shall be disposed of in receptacles designated for this purpose. The
burning of trash or garbage is prohibited. It is unlawful to transport trash, garbage or any other matter to any
park for the purpose of disposal.
6. Township Property - No person shall damage, deface, destroy or remove any park property, including but not
limited to: signs, structures, equipment, natural growth or other material.
7. Motor Vehicles –No person shall operate, stop or park any motor vehicle except on park roads, parking areas or
other areas so designated for such use. Nor shall any person operate any motor vehicle in a reckless or
negligent manner, in excess of the posted speed limit, or in such a manner as to become a nuisance to other
park users or persons occupying adjacent property
8. Firearms - No person other than an officer of the law shall carry any firearm within the limits of the parks.
9. Building of Fires - No person shall set or maintain any fire in the parks except in stoves or grills or fireplaces
maintained for the purpose and located by authority of the Township.
10. Pets/Animals - Pets/animals are not allowed in the parks.
11. Notices - No person shall deface or destroy any notice, or sign posted at any place within the parks or open
space areas by authority of the Township, nor shall any person post any notice or placard at any place within
the parks other than by authority of the Township.
12. Dangerous Athletic Equipment - No person shall use javelins, arrows, discus or similar athletic equipment
dangerous in character unless the Township has expressly permitted the use. The use of baseballs (hardball)
is limited to developed ball fields.
13. Sound Equipment - No person shall use any sound amplification equipment in a Township park.
14. Explosives and Fireworks - No person shall have in his/her possession or ignite any fireworks (fireworks shall
be defined by the National Fire Protection Association standards).
15. Golf - The playing or practicing of golf is prohibited.
16. Skateboards - The use of skateboards is prohibited.
17. All terrain vehicles (ATV’s), mini-bikes, dirt bikes, trailers, and commercial vehicles (except those making
deliveries) are prohibited.
18. Boot Road Park – Ball fields located at Boot Road Park are for baseball and softball use only.</groundspeak:long_description>
      <groundspeak:encoded_hints>
      </groundspeak:encoded_hints>
      <groundspeak:logs>
        <groundspeak:log id="155178322">
          <groundspeak:date>2011-04-17T23:08:37Z</groundspeak:date>
          <groundspeak:type>Found it</groundspeak:type>
          <groundspeak:finder id="1790402">dmcassel</groundspeak:finder>
          <groundspeak:text encoded="False">First GPS read had us looking in the wrong place, but a quick look at the map fixed us up. Found with dawnie22 and our girls. </groundspeak:text>
        </groundspeak:log>
      </groundspeak:logs>
      <groundspeak:travelbugs/>
    </groundspeak:cache>
  </wpt>