<wpt lat="39.5269" lon="-75.811783" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns="http://www.topografix.com/GPX/1/0">
    <time>2008-12-31T08:00:00Z</time>
    <name>GC1J8BR</name>
    <desc>Maryland Municipal League Geotrail Chesapeake City by Maryland Municipal League, Traditional Cache (1.5/1.5)</desc>
    <url>http://www.geocaching.com/seek/cache_details.aspx?guid=4fe1e179-35b6-4deb-b36d-f0944baa03bf</url>
    <urlname>Maryland Municipal League Geotrail Chesapeake City</urlname>
    <sym>Geocache Found</sym>
    <type>Geocache|Traditional Cache</type>
    <groundspeak:cache id="1056692" available="False" archived="True" xmlns:groundspeak="http://www.groundspeak.com/cache/1/0">
      <groundspeak:name>Maryland Municipal League Geotrail Chesapeake City</groundspeak:name>
      <groundspeak:placed_by>Maryland Municipal League</groundspeak:placed_by>
      <groundspeak:owner id="1946055">MML Geotrail</groundspeak:owner>
      <groundspeak:type>Traditional Cache</groundspeak:type>
      <groundspeak:container>Regular</groundspeak:container>
      <groundspeak:difficulty>1.5</groundspeak:difficulty>
      <groundspeak:terrain>1.5</groundspeak:terrain>
      <groundspeak:country>United States</groundspeak:country>
      <groundspeak:state>Maryland</groundspeak:state>
      <groundspeak:short_description html="True">&lt;center&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;b&gt;&lt;font color="maroon"&gt;&lt;font size="4"&gt;&lt;font face="comic sans ms"&gt;The
Maryland Municipal League Geocache Trail&lt;br /&gt;
 Celebrating Maryland’s Cities and Towns.&lt;br /&gt;
MML District 10&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a rel="nofollow"
href="http://www.mdmunicipal.org/mmlhome/index.cfm"&gt;&lt;img src="http://img.geocaching.com/user/display/fddccd9d-f42a-4877-ab64-9c53e29a13e7.jpg" /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/center&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;</groundspeak:short_description>
      <groundspeak:long_description html="True">&lt;center&gt;
&lt;font color="blue"&gt;&lt;font size="4"&gt;&lt;font face="comic sans ms"&gt;The
printed MML Passport is no longer available. However, you may
download a copy from the MML website
&lt;a href="http://www.mdmunicipal.org/programs/geocache.cfm"&gt;here.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;br /&gt;

&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/font&gt;
&lt;center&gt;&lt;font color="blue"&gt;&lt;font size="4"&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;font color="maroon"&gt;&lt;font size="4"&gt;&lt;font face="comic sans ms"&gt;The
trail consists of 11 MML Districts (regions).&lt;br /&gt;
The MML Geocache Trail project will launch January 1, 2009 with 78
participating cities and towns. A trackable geo coin will be given
to the first 500 geocachers as an incentive for locating at least 2
municipal caches in each of the 11 districts. To be eligible for
the coin, geocachers must pick up a Passport at any of the
designated county visitor centers. Geocachers must use the stamp in
the cache on their Passports and write down the cache code word
listed in each cache. After at least two municipal caches in each
district are discovered, geocachers may return to one of the county
visitor centers and have their Passports validated to receive their
collectable coin.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
 For a complete list of participating visitor centers visit the MML
web site at http://www.mdmunicipal.org/mmlhome/index.cfm or MGS web
site at www.mdgps.org.&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/center&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;center&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;img src="http://img.geocaching.com/cache/c332030f-c16a-4307-8155-26fa8cade447.jpg" /&gt;
&lt;/center&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;center&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Welcome to Chesapeake City. On the waterfront here, you can sit
back and relax, watch the sailboats slowly sail by, the jet skiers
and the powerboats zip in and out, and the huge seafaring boats get
a tug up the canal. The 14-mile, hand-dug Chesapeake &amp;amp; Delaware
Canal was opened to traffic on October 17, 1829. At that time there
were three buildings on the south bank at the western end of the
canal. As the ship traffic through the canal increased, the little
cluster of buildings grew into a busy commercial community
providing goods and services to passengers and shippers. In 1839,
the location was named Chesapeake City. By 1849 the city extended
over to the north bank and was well established and at its
population peak. For the next 75 years, Chesapeake City
prospered.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In 1927, the C&amp;amp;D Canal was dredged to a sea-level waterway,
eliminating the need for ships to stop for the locks at Chesapeake
City. The town’s economic base quickly declined. Commerce was
further complicated in 1942 when a ship destroyed the bridge that
connected the two sides of the town, leaving residents and
travelers with only a ferry as a means to cross the canal for seven
years. The opening of a new high-level bridge in 1949 did nothing
to restore the town’s economy—travelers swept by high above the
town. Another blow struck the town in the 1960s when an entire
street of 39 homes was razed to make way for a widening of the
canal, which by then was the third busiest in the world.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Today, Chesapeake City is the only town in Maryland that is
situated on a working commercial canal. Most of its interesting
19th-century architecture remains intact, and the area that
encompasses it on the south bank has been placed on the National
Register of Historic Places. At the city dock, pleasure boaters
find a tranquil harbor off the busy Inter-Coastal Waterway, of
which the canal is a major element. From the basin, visitors can
walk easily into town to tour the Canal Museum, where the story of
the canal is told and the massive waterwheel and steam engines that
filled the locks stand in mute testimony. Outside is a replica of
the lighthouses that once lined the canal.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Chesapeake City now is a destination widely known for its unique
inland view of ocean-going vessels, for the proudly preserved and
displayed reminders of its history, and for its friendly
hospitality. From its origin as a rough and rowdy boom town,
through an era of dispiriting depression, Chesapeake City has
emerged as a charming and interesting place with a warm welcome for
its visitors.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;b&gt;The town of Chesapeake City thanks you for visiting!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;img src="http://img.geocaching.com/cache/12278ee9-7d9e-4a97-881d-ba79064ed7d8.jpg" /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Thanks to CodyHollowFarm for helping with this hide!&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a rel="nofollow"
href="http://www.mdgps.org"&gt;&lt;font color="indigo"&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;font size="3"&gt;&lt;font face="comic sans ms"&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
 &lt;img src="http://www.mdgps.org/Mdgpsmember2.gif" /&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/center&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;center&gt;&lt;b&gt;Thanks to the Maryland Geocaching Society for assisting
with this project!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/center&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;/center&gt;</groundspeak:long_description>
      <groundspeak:encoded_hints>Pretty scenery, pretty flowers! Don't look too high, but bend and look.</groundspeak:encoded_hints>
      <groundspeak:logs>
        <groundspeak:log id="122834249">
          <groundspeak:date>2010-08-20T07:00:00Z</groundspeak:date>
          <groundspeak:type>Found it</groundspeak:type>
          <groundspeak:finder id="1790402">dmcassel</groundspeak:finder>
          <groundspeak:text encoded="False">2nd today</groundspeak:text>
        </groundspeak:log>
      </groundspeak:logs>
      <groundspeak:travelbugs/>
    </groundspeak:cache>
  </wpt>