<wpt lat="40.049367" lon="-75.661933" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns="http://www.topografix.com/GPX/1/0">
    <time>2009-02-14T08:00:00Z</time>
    <name>GC1MNFT</name>
    <desc>Willard Scott is Watching YOU!! by S. I. C. K., Traditional Cache (1/1)</desc>
    <url>http://www.geocaching.com/seek/cache_details.aspx?guid=8499d0d9-e372-4e36-9f43-e4bb4be90ec5</url>
    <urlname>Willard Scott is Watching YOU!!</urlname>
    <sym>Geocache Found</sym>
    <type>Geocache|Traditional Cache</type>
    <groundspeak:cache id="1128892" available="False" archived="True" xmlns:groundspeak="http://www.groundspeak.com/cache/1/0">
      <groundspeak:name>Willard Scott is Watching YOU!!</groundspeak:name>
      <groundspeak:placed_by>S. I. C. K.</groundspeak:placed_by>
      <groundspeak:owner id="83789">Kin9sPanK</groundspeak:owner>
      <groundspeak:type>Traditional Cache</groundspeak:type>
      <groundspeak:container>Micro</groundspeak:container>
      <groundspeak:difficulty>1</groundspeak:difficulty>
      <groundspeak:terrain>1</groundspeak:terrain>
      <groundspeak:country>United States</groundspeak:country>
      <groundspeak:state>Pennsylvania</groundspeak:state>
      <groundspeak:short_description html="True">Venture behind enemy lines to retrieve this cache from the most
evil empire in existence today.&lt;br /&gt;</groundspeak:short_description>
      <groundspeak:long_description html="True">When I mention Willard Scott, do you immediately think of the
rotund Today Show weather man who was totally infatuated with
centenarians? That was in the 1980s, but did you realize that
Willard was a Bozo way before that?&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Yes, before the Today Show, Willard Scott, in the early 1960s was
Bozo the Clown. He was responsible for terrorizing a whole
generation of children and was the inspiration for Steven Kin9's
Pennywise character. But even this is only the tip of the iceberg
of the damage he has unleashed on the unsuspecting American
Public.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
In the mid 1960s, Willard Scott would join forces with Satan
himself and align with the most evil empire that the world has
seen. Their very symbol instills fear into the hearts of people all
over the globe who's only crime is a desire to stay healthy.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Willard Scott would, for a short time, become the Supreme Minister
of Corporate Propaganda for this Hideous Evil Empire when he
released his alter ego, a freak of nature named Ronald.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
He was just recently awarded the Distinguished Iron Arches by his
Corporate Overlords for his role in the fattening of humanity and
the disruption of Geocaching all over the World. You see that
Willard takes pride in stuffing our Geocaches with hideous and
broken McToys.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
So the next time you find a cache filled with broken McToys, or
when the Red and Yellow Flying Saucers come to Earth and the aliens
ask how they can serve man, you better run (or waddle) for cover
and thank Willard Scott for facilitating the destruction of
civilization as we know it.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
You have been warned.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;</groundspeak:long_description>
      <groundspeak:encoded_hints>Pretend that you are Willard Scott and that Light Post is a Centenarian.</groundspeak:encoded_hints>
      <groundspeak:logs>
        <groundspeak:log id="136400566">
          <groundspeak:date>2010-11-20T04:41:16Z</groundspeak:date>
          <groundspeak:type>Found it</groundspeak:type>
          <groundspeak:finder id="1790402">dmcassel</groundspeak:finder>
          <groundspeak:text encoded="False">Quick find with dawnie22 on the way home from dinner</groundspeak:text>
        </groundspeak:log>
      </groundspeak:logs>
      <groundspeak:travelbugs/>
    </groundspeak:cache>
  </wpt>