<wpt lat="39.940917" lon="-75.727233" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns="http://www.topografix.com/GPX/1/0">
    <time>2010-04-11T07:00:00Z</time>
    <name>GC26M0J</name>
    <desc>Here Rests INDIAN HANNAH by SquirtGunn, Traditional Cache (1.5/1.5)</desc>
    <url>http://www.geocaching.com/seek/cache_details.aspx?guid=94eb3d2e-18ef-429c-aee7-124bb391ecf0</url>
    <urlname>Here Rests INDIAN HANNAH</urlname>
    <sym>Geocache Found</sym>
    <type>Geocache|Traditional Cache</type>
    <groundspeak:cache id="1633906" available="True" archived="False" xmlns:groundspeak="http://www.groundspeak.com/cache/1/0">
      <groundspeak:name>Here Rests INDIAN HANNAH</groundspeak:name>
      <groundspeak:placed_by>SquirtGunn</groundspeak:placed_by>
      <groundspeak:owner id="718637">SquirtGunn</groundspeak:owner>
      <groundspeak:type>Traditional Cache</groundspeak:type>
      <groundspeak:container>Small</groundspeak:container>
      <groundspeak:difficulty>1.5</groundspeak:difficulty>
      <groundspeak:terrain>1.5</groundspeak:terrain>
      <groundspeak:country>United States</groundspeak:country>
      <groundspeak:state>Pennsylvania</groundspeak:state>
      <groundspeak:short_description html="False">
      </groundspeak:short_description>
      <groundspeak:long_description html="False">Working ‘mid my marigolds and zinnias,
I found some arrow-heads the other day- 
Straight I journeyed in imagination 
To an earlier era far away. 
When those Newlin Township hills were peopled 
By an older, simpler race than ours, 
Folk, perchance with little time for musing 
‘Mid low orchard boughs and summer flowers, 
Little time to watch the slow unfolding Of the silken-petalled hollyhocks 
And the strange and fragrant fascination Of pungent peonies and purple phlox. 
Or did perhaps those simple forest children 
Look with wistful wonder now and then
On wild daisies dancing on a hilltop 
Or Quaker ladies in a mossy glen? 
While their fathers tracked the fleet-footed foxes,
Did the little woodland children there
Gather berry-blooms to weave in garlands 
And roses wild to wind among their hair?
I can picture one bright, dark-eyed damsel
Roaming often by Wawassan’s stream, 
Wandering far apart from all her playmates 
By those grassy shores to muse and dream; 
Happy in her world of winds and waters, 
Clouds and leaping fish and warbling birds; 
Learning nature’s secrets through the seasons,
Chanting of her love in liquid words.
In these ancient meadows here about us 
Stood the wigwam of her infant days;
Here her father set forth on his hunting, 
Here her mother worked their patch of maize.
Here the maiden watched the summer sunsets,
Heard the frozen forest’s wintry roar,
Heard the hills re-echo songs of triumph
As the warriors hastened home from war. 
Here she heard the tribal incantations 
Chanted to a wild and wizard tune,
Here she joined the mystic tribal dances
Underneath the drowsy harvest moon. 
And wherever was her future biding, 
To whatever valleys she might roam, 
Still she cherished lifelong recollections 
Of those ancient fields, her childhood home. 
Now besides the waters of the Wawassan, 
Northward from these meadows of her birth,
Lies the last of Chester County’s Indians, 
Wrapt in slumber in the quiet earth.</groundspeak:long_description>
      <groundspeak:encoded_hints>
      </groundspeak:encoded_hints>
      <groundspeak:logs>
        <groundspeak:log id="152275681">
          <groundspeak:date>2011-04-02T19:41:38Z</groundspeak:date>
          <groundspeak:type>Found it</groundspeak:type>
          <groundspeak:finder id="1790402">dmcassel</groundspeak:finder>
          <groundspeak:text encoded="False">Pretty quick find. Neat to see the memorial. TFTC</groundspeak:text>
        </groundspeak:log>
      </groundspeak:logs>
      <groundspeak:travelbugs/>
    </groundspeak:cache>
  </wpt>