<wpt lat="40.22665" lon="-74.09465" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns="http://www.topografix.com/GPX/1/0">
    <time>2010-04-19T07:00:00Z</time>
    <name>GC27489</name>
    <desc>Bowling Memories - Fantasy by RedHotRutabaga, Traditional Cache (1/1)</desc>
    <url>http://www.geocaching.com/seek/cache_details.aspx?guid=d3dfc334-6346-452e-9957-99cbaff5a42b</url>
    <urlname>Bowling Memories - Fantasy</urlname>
    <sym>Geocache Found</sym>
    <type>Geocache|Traditional Cache</type>
    <groundspeak:cache id="1648560" available="True" archived="False" xmlns:groundspeak="http://www.groundspeak.com/cache/1/0">
      <groundspeak:name>Bowling Memories - Fantasy</groundspeak:name>
      <groundspeak:placed_by>RedHotRutabaga</groundspeak:placed_by>
      <groundspeak:owner id="2873794">RedHotRutabaga</groundspeak:owner>
      <groundspeak:type>Traditional Cache</groundspeak:type>
      <groundspeak:container>Small</groundspeak:container>
      <groundspeak:difficulty>1</groundspeak:difficulty>
      <groundspeak:terrain>1</groundspeak:terrain>
      <groundspeak:country>United States</groundspeak:country>
      <groundspeak:state>New Jersey</groundspeak:state>
      <groundspeak:short_description html="False">Another cache &amp; dash</groundspeak:short_description>
      <groundspeak:long_description html="False">Bowling Memories – Fantasy

This cache is the third in a series of caches that will be at or near locations of bowling centers in NJ that are no more. Each location will start with some stories and hopefully some pictures from back in the day when they were vibrant bowling centers and not the office complexes, parking lots, or, worse yet, landfill that you see today. Please add your stories and/or pics to keep their MEMORIES alive!

Fantasy Lanes was an 80 lane state-of-the-art bowling center conveniently located near the intersections of Rt. 33, Rt. 66, and the Garden State Parkway where the Jersey Shore Premium Outlets now stand. You would walk in the front door to the main counter, flanked by 20 lanes on each side. On the second level were an additional 20 lanes on each side, which had a view of the main concourse. Looking past the front counter on the back wall on the left was your typical snack bar serving the standard fare of pizza, hot dogs, and fries. Right next to that was a 50s-style soda fountain decked out in black, white, and chrome as far as the eye could see.

Fantasy Lanes was equipped with state-of-the-art computer scoring that was very progressive for the early 1980s. The consoles even indicated ball speed. Talk about being far ahead of its time.

Some of the best times were had on Saturday nights when they broke out the fog machines and laser light shows. The overhead lights sparkled in the dim fog as the one-hit-wonders blared out of the speakers over the lanes. The crowd, decked out in their neon-colored parachute pants, scrunchy socks, and Chuck Taylor high tops, came to Fantasy Lanes to “SEE” and “BE SEEN”. 

Don’t seem to remember Fantasy Lanes? Really? Because that’s exactly what it was. It was all a fantasy of a younger RedHotRutabaga growing up in the neighboring town of Neptune. Hey, I used to want a horse too!

Enjoy! And bring your own pen.

Check out the other caches in the series as they get published:

Intro: 	      Bowling Memories – Laurel (GC24JY0)
1.	Bowling Memories – Neptune (GC26DG6)
2.	Bowling Memories – Barclay (GC26DGV)</groundspeak:long_description>
      <groundspeak:encoded_hints>
      </groundspeak:encoded_hints>
      <groundspeak:logs>
        <groundspeak:log id="205621708">
          <groundspeak:date>2011-12-31T16:11:03Z</groundspeak:date>
          <groundspeak:type>Found it</groundspeak:type>
          <groundspeak:finder id="1790402">dmcassel</groundspeak:finder>
          <groundspeak:text encoded="False">Quick find after visiting relatives. Found with dawnie22 and 19acassel. </groundspeak:text>
        </groundspeak:log>
      </groundspeak:logs>
      <groundspeak:travelbugs/>
    </groundspeak:cache>
  </wpt>