<wpt lat="40.056833" lon="-75.672733" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns="http://www.topografix.com/GPX/1/0">
    <time>2010-08-01T07:00:00Z</time>
    <name>GC2CNFF</name>
    <desc>Surroundin9 the Castle - The Crowning Glory! by The Fair Maidens of Chesco, Traditional Cache (1/1)</desc>
    <url>http://www.geocaching.com/seek/cache_details.aspx?guid=fc23c1df-d55b-49ba-a146-2b44aad9cb94</url>
    <urlname>Surroundin9 the Castle - The Crowning Glory!</urlname>
    <sym>Geocache Found</sym>
    <type>Geocache|Traditional Cache</type>
    <groundspeak:cache id="1814075" available="False" archived="True" xmlns:groundspeak="http://www.groundspeak.com/cache/1/0">
      <groundspeak:name>Surroundin9 the Castle - The Crowning Glory!</groundspeak:name>
      <groundspeak:placed_by>The Fair Maidens of Chesco</groundspeak:placed_by>
      <groundspeak:owner id="3602545">GeoGirls of Chesco</groundspeak:owner>
      <groundspeak:type>Traditional Cache</groundspeak:type>
      <groundspeak:container>Micro</groundspeak:container>
      <groundspeak:difficulty>1</groundspeak:difficulty>
      <groundspeak:terrain>1</groundspeak:terrain>
      <groundspeak:country>United States</groundspeak:country>
      <groundspeak:state>Pennsylvania</groundspeak:state>
      <groundspeak:short_description html="False">Our friend, Kin9sPank, the self proclaimed “Kin9 of Geocaching and Member of the Chester County Caching Royalty” has been claiming authority over these lands since 11/2002. After a recent VICTORY event, he posted the following log:</groundspeak:short_description>
      <groundspeak:long_description html="False">“I am declaring a moratorium on all caches less than two miles from the home coordinates. I just want to take the rest of the summer off of doing nearby caches.”

This did not sit well with the local nobility. Therefore, we are instituting a COUP D’ETAT! And if you don’t think this can be done …… READ THE CROWN!

Our 7th and final siege on the Crown. Oh, and how appropriate it is!

BYOP

------UPDATE---------------UPDATE ---------------- UPDATE-----------------

August 20, 2010 – 
I stopped by this evening to perform the requested maintenance.....to my horror, I found a wretched creature in the place of our well hidden cache. It seems that His Royal Highness, Kin9sPank, had employed the Court Magician to turn this cache into a frog!

Being a member of Chester County Royalty myself, I knew that a simple kiss was all that was needed to fix this dilemma and clear the Needs Maintenance attribute that came along with the transformation. Smooooch!   To my amazement, a prince appeared before my very eyes .... and not just any prince - the Prince of Persia .... Prince Dastan ..... Jake Gyllenhaal!!!!   OK, So maybe this maiden isn't so fair   But the Kin9's magician must be quite powerful as my prince remained the size of the frog   He is now the new sentry on this cache ... you will want to watch out for his sword, please be careful!</groundspeak:long_description>
      <groundspeak:encoded_hints>
      </groundspeak:encoded_hints>
      <groundspeak:logs>
        <groundspeak:log id="176827678">
          <groundspeak:date>2011-08-01T19:02:31Z</groundspeak:date>
          <groundspeak:type>Found it</groundspeak:type>
          <groundspeak:finder id="1790402">dmcassel</groundspeak:finder>
          <groundspeak:text encoded="False">Quick find after a dinner out. Found with dawnie22, 19acassel. </groundspeak:text>
        </groundspeak:log>
      </groundspeak:logs>
      <groundspeak:travelbugs/>
    </groundspeak:cache>
  </wpt>