<wpt lat="38.9165" lon="-77.242767" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns="http://www.topografix.com/GPX/1/0">
    <time>2011-02-14T08:00:00Z</time>
    <name>GC2NV66</name>
    <desc>GrandJ's SSP-2  Sami by GrandJ, Traditional Cache (2/1.5)</desc>
    <url>http://www.geocaching.com/seek/cache_details.aspx?guid=ea3f49c9-c5c8-4e87-aad2-35bd6b972c93</url>
    <urlname>GrandJ's SSP-2  Sami</urlname>
    <sym>Geocache Found</sym>
    <type>Geocache|Traditional Cache</type>
    <groundspeak:cache id="2086711" available="True" archived="False" xmlns:groundspeak="http://www.groundspeak.com/cache/1/0">
      <groundspeak:name>GrandJ's SSP-2  Sami</groundspeak:name>
      <groundspeak:placed_by>GrandJ</groundspeak:placed_by>
      <groundspeak:owner id="2145451">GrandJ</groundspeak:owner>
      <groundspeak:type>Traditional Cache</groundspeak:type>
      <groundspeak:container>Micro</groundspeak:container>
      <groundspeak:difficulty>2</groundspeak:difficulty>
      <groundspeak:terrain>1.5</groundspeak:terrain>
      <groundspeak:country>United States</groundspeak:country>
      <groundspeak:state>Virginia</groundspeak:state>
      <groundspeak:short_description html="False">In the animal world, where one of us works, "SSP" stands for Species Survival Plan, a series of specific plans formulated and administered by zoologists, vets, and other scientists to help make sure our most endangered species won't die out.

SSP coincidentally are the intitials of our first three grandkids:  Spenzi, Sami, and Patrick, which inspired this series.</groundspeak:short_description>
      <groundspeak:long_description html="False">This is no longer a puzzle series----Spenzi, Sami, and Patrick each stand alone.  Ignore the codes on the logsheet.

The series is meant to be fun, easy, quick, so have fun.



It is meant to be a fun, easy, quick series, so have fun.

Sami is petite and intelligent (and maybe a little devious)    A plan for her must consider cleverness and thinking outside the box.  Like Sami, this cache is small.  Remember to bring a pencil and something to note the clue. You will also probably need an extraction tool.

Do not park on the side of the road.  It is very busy.  There is parking in the park a little further along.  And remember parks are closed at dark, so no hunting then.</groundspeak:long_description>
      <groundspeak:encoded_hints>
      </groundspeak:encoded_hints>
      <groundspeak:logs>
        <groundspeak:log id="174079464">
          <groundspeak:date>2011-07-20T18:37:58Z</groundspeak:date>
          <groundspeak:type>Found it</groundspeak:type>
          <groundspeak:finder id="1790402">dmcassel</groundspeak:finder>
          <groundspeak:text encoded="False">Took me a few minutes, but I came away with the smiley. I'm in town on a business trip and was still dressed for work, so I was glad there were no muggles to watch me traipsing around in the woods. </groundspeak:text>
        </groundspeak:log>
      </groundspeak:logs>
      <groundspeak:travelbugs/>
    </groundspeak:cache>
  </wpt>